http://www.airborn.com/about/privacy-statement

Airborn, Inc.
Products
Connectors
W SeriesR SeriesM SeriesN SeriesSeries 360verSI SeriesRC SeriesRCII SeriesZ SeriesmicroQUAD SeriesmicroSI SeriesMacro D
Cable Assemblies
M SeriesmicroQUAD SeriesmicroSI SeriesN SeriesverSI SeriesSpace AOCRugged AOC
Flexible Circuit Assemblies
TYPE I: Single-Sided FlexTYPE II: Double-Sided FlexTYPE III: Multi-Layer FlexTYPE IV: Rigid FlexSculptured® FlexExtended-Length FlexFlex Circuit Assemblies
Military Part Cross Reference
Value-Added Services
Cable AssembliesFlexible Circuit AssembliesContract ManufacturingCircuit BoardsChassis/Box BuildsTesting & Quality Certification
Markets
AerospaceMilitary & DefenseMedical DevicesSpace ExplorationIndustrial
Support
SuppliersDistributorsValue-Added DistributorsFeatured DistributorsCustomer Support
About
HistoryLeadershipOur CustomersLocationsCareersAirBorn QualityContact
Resources
PoliciesProduct DocumentationSupplier DocumentationCatalogs & BrochuresNews & Events
Products
Connectors
M Series
microQUAD Series
microSI Series
N Series
R Series
RC Series
Privacy Statement
AirBorn, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the AirBorn, Inc. website and governs data collection and usage. By using the AirBorn, Inc. website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of Your Personal Information
AirBorn, Inc. collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. AirBorn, Inc. also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by AirBorn, Inc.  This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website address. This information is used by AirBorn, Inc. for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the AirBorn, Inc. website.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through AirBorn, Inc. public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: AirBorn, Inc. does not read any of your private online communications.
AirBorn, Inc. encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from AirBorn, Inc. so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information.  AirBorn, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the AirBorn, Inc. and the AirBorn, Inc. family of websites.
Use of Your Personal Information
AirBorn, Inc. collects and uses your personal information to operate the AirBorn, Inc. website and deliver the services you have requested. AirBorn, Inc. also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from AirBorn, Inc. and its affiliates. AirBorn, Inc. may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
AirBorn, Inc. does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. AirBorn, Inc. may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique, personally-identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, AirBorn, Inc. may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to AirBorn, Inc., and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
AirBorn, Inc. does not use or disclose sensitive personal information without your explicit consent.
AirBorn, Inc. keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within AirBorn, Inc. in order to determine what AirBorn, Inc. services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within AirBorn, Inc. to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
AirBorn, Inc. websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on AirBorn, Inc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of AirBorn, Inc.; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of AirBorn, Inc. or the public.
Use of Cookies
The AirBorn, Inc. website use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a webpage server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize AirBorn, Inc. pages or register with AirBorn, Inc. site or services, a cookie helps AirBorn, Inc. to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same AirBorn, Inc. website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved so you can easily use the AirBorn, Inc. features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the AirBorn, Inc. services or websites you visit.
Security of Your Personal Information
AirBorn, Inc. secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. AirBorn, Inc. secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to This Statement
AirBorn, Inc. will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. AirBorn, Inc. encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how AirBorn, Inc. is protecting your information.
Contact Information
AirBorn, Inc. welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that AirBorn, Inc. has not adhered to this Statement, please contact AirBorn, Inc. at webmaster@airborn.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
© 2020 AirBorn, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
